galaxys6samsung.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy

At **Galaxys6samsung.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This is the privacy policy document that we have created to outlines the types of personal information that we received and collected and how it is used.

**Web Beacons and **Cookies**  
**

Galaxys6samsung.com does use cookies to store our visitors information. We are partner with Google Adsense, Amazon and other ads network and that may use your data for just reference.  
**  
DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Galaxys6samsung.com. It  use the DART cookie to serve ads to users based on their visit to our website and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

We are also affiliated with Amazon and give you related Gadgets and Products based on your interest. The third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Galaxys6samsung.com send directly to your browsers. This type of ads network may receive your IP address when this occurs and they also use advance technologies such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons to track the records for their sells.

We don’t have any kind of access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by commenting here. If you feel that your privacy is not considered or have any issue with the cookies then you can contact us. We will be more than happy to assist you.
